>> Jem Young: 所以，让我们来建立这个领域，我们买了它。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So
let's set up that domain, we bought it.
但是现在如果你去的话它就像一个保留的页面或者一个空白的页面
But right now if you go there it points
to like a holding page or a blank page or
它无法解决任何问题，具体取决于您的主管提供方是谁。
it doesn't resolve anything depending
on who your hosting provider is.
但是，我们要做的是希望将域指向新的服务器。
But what we want to do is we want to
point the domain to the new server.
这就是它变得棘手的地方。
And this is where it gets tricky.
开玩笑的不是那么棘手但会涉及到这些记录
Kidding, it's not that tricky, but
it's going to involve these records and
如果我说，修改你的记录来做这个， t 是没道理的。
if I said, modify your a record to
do this, t wouldn't make any sense.
但现在它确实存在，因为你现在都在这里的 DNS 记录中。
But now it does because you're
all up here now at DNS Records.
所以我们想做的就是把两个 A 记录添加到我们的领域。
So what we want to do is we want to
add two A records to our domain.
我们希望使用作为根域的 @ 。
We want to use the @,
which is the root domain.
例如，jemisththe.最优是我的根域。
So for
instance jemisthe.best is my root domain.
这与 www.jemisthebest的不同。
Which is actually different
from www.jemisthebest.
我很高兴的是这个域名的人我很喜欢这样说
Man that was a good domain name I'm glad,
I like to say that all the time.
我们想让它变得更容易我们可以用 GoDaddy
What we wanna do it to make it easier,
we can use GoDaddy or
Google 域或名称便宜以修改 A 记录。
Google domains or
name cheap to modify the A records.
但我宁愿做些更容易的事
But what I'd rather do, and
I think it's a little bit easier,
我们可以用数字海洋来使用它们的名字
we can use Digital Ocean and
use their name servers, because honestly,
他们的 UI 更容易使用
their UI is just easier to use.
所以我们想做的第一件事就是我们要修改我们的名称服务器
So the first thing we want to do is we
want to modify our name servers from
我们拥有的任何托管供应商的数字海洋。
Digital Ocean on whatever
hosting provider we have.
所以我要走了它会看起来有点不同
So I'm going to walk through that it's
going to look a little different depending
您的域的所有者。
on who owns your domain.
但一般来说，这些步骤都是一样的。
But generally the steps
are always going to be the same.
所以我要回去，我先去数字海洋。
So I'll go back to,
first I'll go with Digital Ocean.
让我们来看看，我要去管理，我相信它是网络。
And let's see, I'm gonna go to manage and
I believe it's networking.
>> Jem Young: 是，我可以做的是，我可以输入最终我
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, so what I can do is I
can enter the domain that eventually I
要为其创建记录。
wanna create records for.
所以我要说的是 ...
So I'm gonna say, jemisthe.best.
现在我要补充这个领域。
And I'm gonna add that domain for now.
然后你就可以在这里说
And then it gives you
the option up here to say Hey,
我想创造一个不同的记录，现在我们要用这个记录。
I want to create a different record right
now we're just going to use the a record.
有人说，现在我后悔不给我的服务器命名更好。
Someone say at and I regret now not
naming my server something better.
我相信是这个
I believe it's this one.
很不错，因为数字海洋一直在跟踪你的微滴
And it's nice because Digital Ocean
keeps track of your droplets and
您的 IP 地址，因此它将自动填充任何 IP 地址。
your IP addresses so it'll
automatically populate whichever one.
无论你想说什么 IP 地址都是基于你的下降
Whichever IP address you wanna point
it to based on the drop that you have.
所以我们可以创造一个记录然后我要另一个
So we can create one record for
that, and then I want another one for
WWW，与仅规范根域不同，
WWW, which is different from
just the canonical root domain,
然后我就直接去看一样的微滴
and then I wanna direct
to the same droplets.
然后我要创造一个新的记录
And then I'm going to create a new record.
>> Jem Young: 那么此时，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So at this point,
您的 DNS 记录位置应该是类似的。
your DNS records location should
look something like this.
上面写着 " 嘿 DNS 记录 " 的记录是录音的
And the a record that says hey DNS
record is hear that a record says,
DNS 记录显示我们又有这些名字服务器
DNS record says here and
then we have these name servers Again,
名称服务器是他们持有地址簿的，他们持有电话簿。
name servers are they hold the address
book, they hold the phone book.
但现在如果你去买你买的任何领域
But right now,
if you go to whatever domain you bought,
它不会重定向到您的 Web 站点。
it's not going to redirect
to your website yet.
那是因为一个，你的服务器没有真正的启动和运行。
That's because one,
your server is not really up and running.
它正在运行，但是它不真正接受名称服务器的连接错误，所以
It's running but it's not really accepting
connections to the name servers wrong So
我们需要做的是更改名称服务器以控制主机
what we need to do is change the name
server to give control to the hosting
说，哎，其实我想用的是数字海洋，同一台服务器，不是你的。
provider to say, hey, actually I want to
use Digital Ocean, same server, not yours.
所以我要复制这个名字
So I'm gonna copy this name.
使用您的托管供应商，我使用的是便宜的名称。
And using whatever your hosting
provider is, I'm using name cheap.
我要去 " 域"
I'm gonna go to Domain.
这是在配置中。
And this is under configuration.
根据你的主人的不同情况会有一点不同
It's gonna look a little bit different
depending on who your host is.
但原则是一样的。
But the principle will be the same.
如果你有问题你只能问 Goaddle GoDaddy 什么的
If you have questions you can
just google GoDaddy or whatever,
更改名称服务器。
change the name server.
好的，所以无论您的主管提供方都在查找名称服务器的更改位置。
Okay, so whatever your hosting provider is
just find where to change the name server.
对于它位于高级 DNS 下的 Namecheap 。
For Namecheap it's under advanced DNS.
我们会去定制 Nameservers。
And we'll go to Custom Nameservers.
其实没有
Actually, no.
我们想去找那人
We wanna go to not Find Nameservers.
我们要添加名称服务器。
We wanna go to Add Nameserver.
>> Jem Young: 其实，这也不正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Actually,
that isn't correct, too.
我以前也这么做过，总是强调我的名字，因为它的名字。
I did this before and it always stress
me out because the way it's named.
在域上。
It's on domain.
好吧，我忘了域，还有名字的服务器
All right, I forgot it's under domain and
there's also name servers
在 " 高级 DNS " 下但那是我们想做的
under Advanced DNS, but
that's something we wanna go with.
我们想和传统的 DNS一起去
We wanna go with custom DNS.
我只是想把它贴在数字海洋名称服务器上。
And I'm just gonna paste in
the Digital Ocean name server.
记住我从这儿抢到的
Remember, I grabbed that from here.
它通常有一，二，三，几乎都是托管服务提供商。
It's usually ns one and ns two and
ns three for almost all hosting providers.
然后再贴在这个上
And going to paste on this.
要移动点 i 不知道您何时复制使用复制命令
Going to move the dot i don't know
when you copy use the copy command
数字海洋就是这样
Digital Ocean does that.
我不认为事情很重要但我喜欢把它去掉
I don't think it matters but
I like to remove it anyways.
我要给服务器三个名字
And I'm just going to
give name server three.
多ts
Dots.
那我就去打这个支票标记
Then I'm gonna hit this check mark save.
> > Jem Young: 我在做什么，我们刚刚做的就是移动规范记录。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What I'm doing, so what I we
just did was we move the canonical record.
如果我去杰姆是最好的记录
The record of, if I go to jem is the best.
我现在已经移动了那个记录到数字海洋的人
I moved who owns that record
to Digital Ocean now.
所以现在
So now.
他们一旦控制了 30 号公路就会被控制
They're going to be once the route
30 means once control it might
48 小时后才能生效
take 48 hours to take effect.
可能需要 30， 20， 30 分钟才能更新，因为它们是海量的记录
It might take 30, 20, 30 minutes to update
again because they're massive records and
他们将所有权转移到互联网上
they're shifting ownership
over the internet and
现在有服务器来协调这些东西
there's servers now to coordinate and
all these things like that.
因此，在我们完成服务器设置时，请给它一些时间。
So give it some time it will probably take
by the time we finished our server setup,
它应该准备好了
it should be ready to go.
但它不会立即准备好
But it won't be ready immediately,
因为这些事情会随着时间的延长而延长，所有这类的事情都要结束了。
because these things take time to expire
then renew and all that type of things.
到目前为止有什么问题吗
Any questions so far?
和我一起吗
Everybody with me?
我知道这有点烦人
I know that was a little tedious, but
我们要做的是如何将一个域指向一个服务器。
we're doing that nitty gritty of how do
you actually point a domain to a server.